Juma Ehsani

3434 S 144th St Apt 335

Tukwila, WA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Juma-Ehsani/abb60cb1fa99c5f9

To become a member of a well-disciplined, competed and dynamic organization, where I could prove my carrier-oriented, energetic and self-motivated personality with enough experience, strong communication, interpersonal and analytic skills gained working in multiple organizations. Willing to relocate Anywhere Authorized to work in the US for any employer.

= WORK EXPERIENCE: I have almost 8 years of Work experience in field of IT/Admin in various organizations including the US Army-Afghan Barez Afghan, Red Crescent Society (ARCS), Kardan University and International NGOs.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Package Handler

BBSI - Kent, WA -

February 2017 to Present

BBCI Foot Production Company -USA WA- February 2017 update Working.

Product and packaging.

Network Administrator

Organization: Afghan Red Crescent Society (ARCS) - Kabul -

February 2011 to November 2016

= IT Network Administrator

Organization: Afghan Red Crescent Society (ARCS) - Kabul - February 2011 to September 2016

Responsibilities:

- · Responding to all technical support call/email and assigns technicians for troubleshooting network.
- Ensure timely installation and upgrading of LAN/WAN information systems anti-virus and industry standard applications, etc.
- Set up, maintain and monitor Active Directory, DNS, Microsoft Exchange Server, File Server, and Web Server accordingly.
- Trained technicians on how to troubleshoot and install Mac OSX system applications, printing system and applications.
- Perform other related task as required.

IT Associate

Afghan Barez US Army (Part time during Night) - Kabul -

February 2011 to February 2013

Duties and responsibilities:

- Responding to all technical support calls/email and assigns technicians for troubleshooting & Network;
 Ensure timely installation and upgrading of LAN/WAN information systems anti-virus and industry standard applications, etc.
- · Collaborating with LAN Administrator for new email request;
- · Perform other related task as required.

IT Officer

Kardan University - Kabul -

January 2009 to January 2011

Duties and responsibilities:

- Respond to all technical support call/email and assigns technicians for troubleshooting network;
- Ensure timely installation and upgrading of LAN/WAN information systems anti-virus and industry standard applications, etc.
- Support in inventory control of IT equipment's;
- Keep record of ICT support equipment in database and update required documents;
- Provision inputs to prepare result-oriented work plans
- Maintain and up-to-date inventory of software and hardware of Kardan University;
- · Perform other related task as required.

EDUCATION

12th in IT

Graduated from Habibia High School, Kabul - Kabul

August 1996 to August 2008

CERTIFICATIONS/LICENSES

CCNA Routing & Switching CERTIFICATIONS/LICENSES

December 2014 to January 2015

Completed CCNA Course at GIT Cisco Academy, Bangalore India

Microsoft Certified Systems Engineer (MCSE)

April 2015 to February 2016

Completed MCSE 2012 Course at Zoom Byte Cisco Training Center.

CompTIA Network+

January 2010 to March 2010

Completed Configuration Wireless Network Professional + Comp TIA Network+

Diploma in Information Technology (DIT)

January 2008 to December 2009

Gained Diploma in Information Technology (DIT) from Kardan University, Studied Microsoft Office Package (word, excel, power point, etc.)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Language skills: Language Read Write Speak Understand English Working-knowledge Dari Native

References

Jafari Mohammad ,TRAC Associates Case Manager

Contact # [...]

Email: mj@tracassoc.com

= Britt Greenland English Teacher at High line College

Contact # (425) [...]

Email: bgreenland@highline.edu

= Abdulrahman Kalantary Disaster Management Director at Afghan Red Crescent Society (ARCS)

Contact #: [...]

Email: abrk99@yahoo.com Email: kalantary@redcrescent.af